/** Question set of Europe mountains when the europe button is clicked */
let europe =[
    {
        "question": "Which mountain is Europes tallest peak and is located in the Caucasus Mountains?",
        "choices":["Grossglockner","Mt.Elbrus","Dufourspitze"],
        "correct": "Mt.Elbrus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mountain in Georgia has an elevation of 5,193m ?",
        "choices":["Mount Kazbek","Mont Blanc","Shkhara"],
        "correct": "Shkhara"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mountain is located in Switzerland and has an elevation of 4,634 m?",
        "choices":["Galtymore","Dufourspitze","Carnedd Llewelyn"],
        "correct": "Dufourspitze"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mountain is located in Austria and has an elevation of 3,798 m?",
        "choices":["Grossglockner ","Dufourspitze","Galdhøpiggen"],
        "correct": "Grossglockner "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mountain rises to an astonishing 4,809 m in elevation and is known as 'White Mountain'?",
        "choices":["Helvellyn","Shkhara","Mont Blanc"],
        "correct": "Mont Blanc"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mountain is located in Italy and has an elevation of 4,809 m?",
        "choices":["Nephin","Monte Bianco","Mt. Aneto"],
        "correct": "Monte Bianco"
    },

];

/** Question set for North America mountains when the NA is clicked */
let world = [
    {
        "question": "Which mountain is also known as Mount McKinley and is the tallest mountain in North America.?",
        "choices":["Denali ","Monte Bianco","Mt. Aneto"],
        "correct": "Denali"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mountain is the second tallest mountain in the U.S. Which mountain is this?",
        "choices":["Mount Whitney","Mount Saint Elias","Mt. Bona"],
        "correct": "Mount Saint Elias"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest mountain peak in Canada with an elevation of 19,551 feet (5,959 meters)?",
        "choices":["Mt. Hunter","Mt. Fairweather","Mt. Bona"],
        "correct": "Mt. Logan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the longest mountain range in the US and Canada stretching over 3,000 miles (4,800 kilometers)?",
        "choices":["Mt. Bear","The Rocky Mountains","Laurentian Mountains"],
        "correct": "The Rocky Mountains"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the oldest mountain range in the US and Canada?",
        "choices":["Alaska Range","Mt. Whitney","Appalachian Mountains"],
        "correct": "Appalachian Mountains"
    },
    {
    "question": "Which mountain range extends from the Yukon to the South of British Columbia?",
    "choices":["Coast Mountains","Teton Range","Gaspé Peninsula"],
    "correct": "Coast Mountains"
    },

]